Good evening.
In this show...
six strangers live together
under one roof.
All the show provides...
is a nice house and nice cars.
As always, there is no script.
Things haven't been going well
between Kenken and Ryo-chan.
It kinda now seems like
he's putting things on hold.
You know how I said I had something
important to say?
I thought I was going to convey
my feelings.
-To say that I liked you.
-Yeah.
But, what I need to be doing now
is focus on water polo.
That's what I realized
when I went to this tournament.
I want you to be able to watch me
working my hardest.
Then, he said he has
a game in Wakayama.
And, from there,
out came the trendy.
Miss I-Do-What-I-Want
tells her to "go after him."
You should go and surprise him!
To Wakayama?
Wouldn't that be creepy?
It wouldn't be, not at all.
You really need to go.
-The riskiness is swelling up.
-Yeah, totally.
If she's stealthy about it, it'll be okay.
But I don't think she can be stealthy.
Seina would probably tag along!
I feel like she would.
What? You're kidding, right?
And then, last week,
nothing happened...
-Nothing trendy.
-...between Seina-san and Ma-kun.
Remember when you went out
to eat with Ma-kun?
Ma-kun wasn't that angry,
and it was a misunderstanding?
The day we went out to eat,
he was already leaving to go abroad.
He's probably still there now.
He said he'd be away for about 2 weeks.
I think it'd be good for them
to talk once he comes back.
She said she wants
to fix their relationship,
but she wasn't sure
how to go about doing it.
I wonder if Ma-kun will be
back this week?
-He must surely already have come back, no?
-Oh, yeah?
On his way back from abroad,
perhaps we'll see some more
airport trendiness?
I want to see those two
being trendy at the airport.
Ah, we're all here!
Yeah.
-After so long.
-It's really been so long.
I was also thinking that
when I came down.
What is it, what is it?
-There they are!
-Tickets!
These are for...
your stage show, right?
These are for Saturday, the 7th.
I was hoping you would all
be able to come.
Yup, I'll be there.
In the afternoon?
Yeah, Saturday at 1pm.
Okay.
-Hope you can come.
-Sorry, I can't.
-You won't be able to? I see.
-I have work.
I can't make it,
but I want a ticket.
Ah, okay.
For these, it's has be the 7th.
But otherwise,
there's still spots on other days.
This is just the first day.
So if you make it to Tokyo, come!
-I wanna go, I wanna go!
-If you can work out the timing.
-Okay, let's go together!
-Yeah.
I'll go! Ticket, please.
I'll be waiting. Thanks.
I wanted to go.
-You confident on your acting?
-Yeah, of course.
-All perfect?
-Yeah.
-Oh!
-Impressive.
That's awesome.
Saying that it's perfect.
I can't be saying
I'm not confident.
That's true.
Won't people be wondering
what they're watching?
If we're doing things we're not confident in,
in front of others.
-That's wonderful.
-You've got a point.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Back from a run.
You just came from a run?
So after lunch, you got practice again?
Yeah.
You're on a roll.
My tournament's
coming up in September.
But I have to get my
physical fitness back into shape.
Part of me now feels like
I have to change over.
So best of luck
to you, too, Ippei-chan!
I'll do my best.
-I'll be coming to watch.
-Yeah, of course.
CHIGASAKI
Thanks for waiting.
-Ah, welcome, it's been a while.
-I'm back.
You seemed quite busy.
Yeah, but it was awesome.
It was?
The waves were so good,
and America was awesome, too.
-Were you busy?
-Yeah.
With your thing?
Yeah.
The real deal is coming up soon.
Coming up soon?
Like your backflips?
-Yeah, gotta do my backflips.
-All good?
-Yeah, I'm good now with my backflips.
-No way, I knew you could do 'em.
Naw, naw, naw.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
The real deal's gonna be in Yokohama.
So yeah...
you should come watch.
Seriously?
On opening day.
Yeah.
I'd be so happy to.
I so wanted to come.
Please do.
Tecchan's big spotlight moment.
Come to think of it,
I've never seen you working before.
For real.
-True.
-I still haven't, right?
Yeah.
-I'll be sure to come.
-Okay.
Translated, Timed & Titled by goob
Corrected by Alice (terracemouse)
TETSUYA SUGAYA, 20 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
SEINA SHIMABUKURO, 27 YEARS OLD
PART-TIME WORKER
IPPEI SHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD
COMEDIAN
RYOKO HIRASAWA, 24 YEARS OLD
SONY MUSIC RECORDS EMPLOYEE
KENYA YASUDA, 25 YEARS OLD
NATIONAL WATER POLO ATHLETE
FRANCES CIHI, 26 YEARS OLD
ARTIST
COSTCO SUBS PRESENTS
Oh.
Good work today.
Good work today,
Little Red Riding Hood.
Little Red...
-You've been drinking?
-Yeah. Want one? Let's drink!
So Tecchan... you've got your
theater performance starting this weekend.
Kenken, you got your thing, too.
Your game? Tournament?
My tournament.
It's the Kansai championship.
On the weekend?
Yeah, Saturday and Sunday.
Tournament-style.
There's a lot of teams in it,
so there'll be a lot of games.
I see.
If you have time,
please come watch sometime.
I really would like to!
Do you have a lot of them?
Well, the domestic games I have
are this week, and in October...
Those are quite spread out.
-...I have the biggest tournament.
-I see.
In Japan. Yeah.
There's still no time when
everyone's come to a game.
So if she goes by herself,
won't it be like, "Woah, what's with this?"
Ryoko-chan's probably
not going to do anything painful,
-so it's okay if she goes to watch.
-For me, I don't... well...
Back when I was in a band,
whenever some bandmate's girl...
was backstage, I'd hate it.
-That's backstage for you.
-Backstage, yeah.
I really hated the bandmates' girls.
Whenever one was backstage,
and she was like,
"Good morning!"
I always was like, "WTF?"
-I'd just not care about that.
-Yeah, not backstage.
So... that's why I think I wouldn't really like
athletes' girlfriends, either.
I doubt that.
Athletes' girlfriends wouldn't be able
to come into the locker room, after all.
-So they wouldn't be like, "Good job, guys."
-So it's okay? It's okay?
Also, for Tetsu...
Isn't this a first
in all of Terrace House?
-He threw a great pass.
-He's finally being of some use.
Giving those two tickets.
Also, those seats were definitely
adjacent, right?
What if they were two away?
No, that'd be...
He'd suck so bad.
It'd be like:
Seina, old man, old man, then Ma-kun.
Old men!
KANAGAWA ARTS THEATER
YOKOHAMA
"TUMBLING FINAL"
If... let's say, you fail, or...
you forget lines,
or anything else happens,
just be sure to do it confidently
as if it's all okay.
Yes, sir.
Ah, over here.
Ah, I'm here?
This is pretty close.
Thank you so much for coming
to the stage performance of Tumbling FINAL.
In the event of an emergency,
staff will be guiding you...
-Oh, wassup?
-'Sup.
...so please promptly follow their instructions.
Also, in the event of any earthquakes,
we may suspend our performance.
-Wassup.
This building is
a seismic base isolated structure,
so for your safety,
we ask that you please remain calm,
and please follow all instructions by staff members.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We will begin our performance shortly.
Those still in the lobby,
please take your seats.
I said to lay out
everything you're all thinking!
Lay it out there?
I'm getting so annoyed
looking at you guys.
Every one of ya
be posing.
If you're suddenly wondering
what to talk about,
you're all the members of the same
rhythmic gym group. Cut the crap and speak!
Mostly your roundabout talking
is getting on everyone's nerves!
How rude, Tsuchiura!
You're the one speaking all weird English
in front of Manamicchi.
Stop pretending to be traveled!
In reality, you're not so deep!
-I... I'm always, always...
-Oh, yeah. When are you--
Let me speak!
I may suck at it, but I'm practicing
way more than others!
But Ito, you're doing a great job
crossing your legs,
and being shoddy with practice.
Be more serious!
The one who's being shoddy
is Kaneko-senpai, apparently!
Number 8: Karasumori High School.
What are you gonna do after this?
I was thinking of heading home.
We should grab tea or something.
Okay.
I still have practice to do.
I'm all pumped up,
thanks to Tecchan. See ya!
Bye-bye.
Good luck, Ippei-chan.
Thanks. See ya.
See ya later, bye.
Shall we go?
YOKOHAMA
Tecchan was awesome, right?
Yeah, he was.
That's gotta be the first time
I've seen Tecchan working in person.
I'm not his mom or anything,
but I think he's really grown into something great.
You've been well?
I've been well.
And you, Ma-kun?
I have been.
Like, the same as always.
Of course.
Gonna eat some?
Ah, yeah.
A bit more?
Just a little more.
Thanks.
Sorry, it got all messy.
The other day...
I feel like I did you wrong.
And I wanted to tell you I'm sorry,
so here we are.
I'm sorry, too.
I got all emotional.
What's new there, though?
Yeah, I'm always like that...
but I won't do that again, so...
Sorry.
I thought since you were like that,
maybe you didn't like me anymore.
That's not the case.
Ma-kun, you always...
put up with all my selfishness...
so even from now on,
you'll still be important to me.
Will you be my friend?
Yeah.
Thank you for liking me.
Why are you crying?
I think this is great.
I know you've been, well,
through a whole lot,
but good luck with everything.
Shall we get going?
What? So it's over?
-No, no, no.
-It can't be over.
This is completely... just...
-to be continued, right?
-Yeah, that's right.
For those who don't get
real trendiness,
you new-gen folk may be like,
"What? It's over!?"
But please relax.
Dammit, we've been tricked!
That's so lovely.
"We've been tricked."
This isn't Seina-san
just failing at her tactics?
Right after confirming
whether he still likes her or not like that,
she'll say something like,
"Oh, but I don't feel that way."
She'll pull back.
Despite that, Ma-kun will
sink his teeth into that.
But this time,
finally, he'll be like,
"Oh, well I should be like that, too!"
Then wouldn't she be like,
"No way?"
For now, I think this is trendiness
to make him think it's really over.
-What?! -I see.
-This goes way too deep.
Well, and Tetsu also pulled off
opening night without a hitch.
-Thank goodness!
-He really worked hard.
He was really awesome!
So I wonder what's next?
Won't everything just end up
standing still?
Well, if the next scene
is going to keep up the trendy,
then it's going to be Ma-kun's turn, next.
That's right.
Maybe suddenly, he'll zoom up
on a motorcycle,
and he'll, like,
throw a helmet at her.
At least that much...
"Hop on."
-"At any rate, hop on."
-Anyone else would be shocked.
But Seina-san would just put on
the helmet without a word.
If that happened in the next clip,
we'd be all like, "There it is!"
WAKAYAMA CITY, WAKAYAMA
AKITA SAN PARK
PREFECTURAL POOL
"2014 KANSAI CHAMPIONSHIP
WATER POLO TOURNAMENT
JUNE 7-8, 2014"
"KASHIWAZAKI BOURBON
WATER POLO CLUB"
WAKAYAMA STATION
KANSAI CHAMPIONSHIP
FINAL MATCH
We will begin the match of
The Kashiwazaki Bourbon Water Polo Club vs.
the Toba Public High School
from Kyoto Prefecture.
TOBA HIGH 1 - 0 BOURBON
WHITE (BOURBON) 12 - 9 BLUE (TOBA, KYOTO)
In first place: The Kashiwazaki
Bourbon Water Polo Club!
CONGRATS & GOOD JOB! SORRY TO BUG YOU,
BUT COULD YOU GIVE ME A CALL WHEN YOU'RE FREE?
Hello.
Hey, how's it going?
Good work. Congratuations!
Huh? Why are you congratulating me?
What? You won, didn't you?
We did. You looked online, huh?
-Why do you think I know?
-Why?
Don't tell me... you were here?
Yeah.
No way!
Yeah, way!
I had no idea!
Wait, so did you leave already?
I didn't. I'm still here.
Oh, I see.
Where are you?
You were here?
No, I was watching over there.
-I totally had no idea!
-Really?
-Sorry.
-Congratuations. Huh?
What for, what for?
-For making you come all this way.
-Not at all.
I gotta say again,
you were really awesome.
-I thought you were so awesome out there.
-You probably had no idea what's going on.
No, I did, I did.
I kinda...
studied up before coming.
-You looked it up?
-I looked it up.
-Did you see when I made those goals?
-Yeah.
-No way!
-Yeah, so like...
that first one you made
was super cool!
Thanks. It's been a long time
since I've been called cool.
You were so super cool!
Really.
But yeah, I'm really glad
you came to see my water polo.
It's made me think
I gotta do my best, too!
-No way!?
-Yeah, starting tomorrow.
-Oh, with work?
-Yeah.
Thanks so much for coming.
I'm so happy.
Where's Ippei-kun and Kenya-kun today?
Oh, right. Where's Kenken?
-You already went to his game, then?
-In Wakayama.
Isn't his game already over, then?
He finished today, but he said he's probably
going back to Niigata with his team.
Ah, I see.
-So, did he win?
-He did, they won the championship!
-Oh, he did! Congratulations!
-That's great he won.
Awesome. Good for him!
Oh yeah, you were
so awesome, too, Tecchan.
Really? Thanks.
I thought, "Tecchan's become so fine!"
-I really wanna go see it now!
-Yeah!
Did you run into Masato-kun?
-I did. Yeah.
-I see.
Did you get to talk?
Yeah, we got to.
But I wonder how it went.
Did you get to tell him sorry?
-Yeah, I did.
-I see.
I really feel that...
Hmm... how can I put this into words?
With Ma-kun, since we were both together here
as the first housemates,
and he really fell for me,
and now we have all this history.
And because of this history,
he's really special to me. Very important.
Therefore...
how would I say this?
If we were to date again,
it'd get all messy again and we'd fight.
And then something'll happen
and we'd break up again, and it'll be bad.
So-- and this is going to sound
too neatly tied-off, but--
I'd rather stay friends
forever and ever and ever with him,
and for him to keep being
a special part of my life.
Yeah.
I see...
Instead of me keeping on
getting emotional and hurting him,
and causing that kind of trouble,
I figure having that kind of relationship is better.
That's what I'm convinced of, for myself.
Yeah, so that was
my answer to him. Yeah.
I wonder if it's over.
Hey! That was A-list actress stuff there!
Man, the A-list actress...
The monologue
of an A-list actress...
"I wonder if it's over."
...that was two-and-a-half pages long.
That was from the book of
Dr. Sugako Hashida, wasn't it?
But surprisingly, if we're going
by character count, it's not that long.
The amazing part about it,
was that it was like, two lines long.
-All that, in this much space...
-A ton of space.
The director had no choice
but to say, "Alright, that's okay."
But because she already poured out
that feeling into it, it was so wonderful.
But it's still not all totally
cleaned up yet, is it?
She did say,
"I wonder if it's over."
What do you think, Omi?
-Hmm, yeah, agreed.
-This is what being trendy is about.
She was not at all like,
"Oh, it's so done, it's so done."
But, "Is it over?"
"I wonder if it's over."
Of course they'd
end it right there.
-That's the chance to end it.
-Yeah, the perfect spot.
I mean, Seina-san just
dishes out those chances to slam the door.
She does make them, indeed.
She puts them out like clockwork.
Really, like clockwork.
"I wonder if it's over."
Slam! Like that.
The door's not closed,
though, really!
Babazono?
That was so nice, when she went over
to Kenken's game. So good.
-That was so heart-throbbing.
-And he won, too. So good.
Now what's next?
-They're basically going out now, right?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, if they were to say,
"We're going out," then...
the two of them would feel like they'd
have to really act like they're a couple,
and that might put pressure
on both of them.
-So, they'd have to "conduct" themselves accordingly?
-Well, instead of that...
Kenken might think
he'd have to play the boyfriend,
and would have
to take her on dates and stuff.
-I see.
-He'd think he'd have to do all that,
so it's probably better that they lose
that kind of burden for the time being.
-Just the right kind of relationship.
-Their feelings are getting across to each other...
-It's the most fun time in a relationship.
-More than friends.
Yeah, so jealous of them.
(*Singer Ayame Goriki's 2013 debut single's MV
featured a school setting, hence the lunch pack.)
It's a lunch pack.*
A lunch pack of Goriki-chan's.*
Like her song, "More an Important Person
Than a Friend to Me."*
Exactly fits them right now.
Nothing but that.
Seina-san said the exact same thing, too.
More an important person than a friend.
A special person.
For now, I guess they would
just decide to be friends.
-But we can't accept that.
-What's up with that, really?
So if there were a total
of 11 chapters of trendiness,
then this should be around
the 7th or 8th chapter, right now.
-That's right.
-This is amazingly the 8th chapter.
Oh, yeah? Then, things are going to move
quite a bit soon enough.
-They'll move quite a bit.
-But since this is so popular,
it'll probably go up to 12 chapters.
-But we're well into the latter half.
-I see!
I see, the trendiness is going
to shoot up from here on out.
I guess they couldn't bust it out back then,
if it wasn't right
in the middle of a smash-hit drama.